Lehui Liao



EMAIL: LOKHUNNNN@GMAIL.COM
PHONE: 5415279882

ADDRESS: 3228 SOUTH CHICAGO STREET, SEATTLE, WA 98118

PROFILE

Just finished full stack coding bootcamp course. Don't have lots of coding experiences, therefore, I am looking for an entry level web Developer job. but I am a fast learner and a team player, with a four years design degree in Guangzhou academy of fine arts.

EXPERIENCE

SALE ASSOCIATE, DAISO; SEATTLE, WA - 2018-PRESENT

- Communicate any problem or issue that requires management assistance.
- A positive attitude, excellent listening skills, and an understanding of guest needs.
- Customer service skills.
- The ability to communicate effectively and professionally with associates and customers.

SALE ASSOCIATE, UNIQLO; SEATTLE, WA - 2018-2020 MAY

- Maintain brand and operational standards (visual, cleanliness, etc.)
- Manage customer needs and exceed expectations by utilizing the UNIQLO service standard, following the UNIQLO Fundamental Principles and saying the 6 standard phrases.
- Be knowledgeable of fitting room standards and assist when needed
- Act as cashier when required by following cashier protocol
- Process shipment and ensure all merchandise is represented on the floor in full size run
- · Assist management to identify and resolve issues in the store
- · Provide product and brand knowledge to customers

- Follow all company policy and procedures & notify management of any infractions
- · Assist with special projects as assigned by management

CAP SERVICES TEST PROCTOR, CENTER OREGON COMMUNITY COLLEGE 2017-2018

- Proctor tests: Proctor the ACCUPLACER placement exam and/or the nursing admission exam (TEAS) according to established procedures. Ensure the security and integrity of the tests and testing environment.
- Follow FERPA and ADA guidelines and protocols.
- Testing process support: Check in and mark attendance for students taking the placement test using the COCC scheduling software or roster reports.
- Provide verbal direction: Answer basic questions regarding COCC testing policy and procedures related to placement testing, course placement and associated test scores and COCC next steps.
- Maintain the Computer Lab/ testing room: Keep the computer-based testing room secure. Keep the room clean and testing materials

SERVER, Q BU LUO, LONGMEN, GUANGDONG 2013-1014

- For restaurant, taking orders, deliver food, interact with customers
- Worked the cashier collecting money for food proving proper change
- Explained menu and food items available for purchase and offered recommendations to customers
- Set table, sat customers, bussed tables, ensured restaurant and tables were clean and ready for customers

EDUCATION

Certification in Full Stack Web + Mobile Development bootcamp

Nucamp - Seattle, WA September 2020 to February 2021

Central Oregon Community College - Bend, OR 2017 to 2018

Bachelor in fashion design

Guangzhou Academy of Fine Arts - Guangzhou, china

September 2012 to July 2016

High school diploma

Huizhou Shiyan High School - Huizhou, china

September 2009 to July 2012

CERTIFICATION

Full Stack Web + Mobile Development bootcamp

September 2020 to February 2021

It's a half year program, learn to code and become a web developer.

The course includes:

- HTML and CSS
- Front-End Web UI Framework, Bootstrap
- Front End JavaScript Library, React
- Multiplatform Mobile App Development with React Native
- Server-side Development with NodeJS, Express and MongoDB

SKILLS

- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe photoshop
- Sigma
- HTML5
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- React
- React Native
- Node.js
- MonogoDB
- Github

LANGUAGES

Cantonese - Expert

Mandarin - Expert

English - Great